

CONTACT

Q Sweden - Malmö

Moussa.Ellakki@hotmail.com

(in) linkedin.com/in/moussaellakki

+46739612818

⊕ <u>GitHu</u>b

Portfolio

SKILLS

- Communication
- Problem solving
- Teamwork
- Swift
- SwiftUI
- UIKit
- MVVM
- MVC
- Cocoapods
- Kotlin
- Java
- C#
- Firebase
- Git & Github
- API Networking
- UI/UX Design
- Figma

LANGUAGE

Swedish Fluent

Enalish Proficient

Arabic Native

MOUSSA EL LAKKI

Android & iOS Developer

I am deeply fascinated by mobile app development.
A quick learner and also a team player who is not afraid to take the lead. Innovation and creativity are my two strong points with a great interest in creating a fantastic user experience.

EDUCATION

MALMÖ YRKESHÖGSKOLA

2021 - 2022 Programmerare IPhone & Android

KOMVUX MALMÖ

2020 - 2021 Programming 2 Java

KOMVUX MALMÖ

2019 - 2020 Programming 1 Java

MALMÖ FOLKHÖGSKOLA

2007 - 2010 High school

EXPERIENCE

TETRA PAK

2017 - 2019 FUNCTIONAL TESTER

I was working as a Functional and technical Tester, and mainly worked with assembling and internal software test

GFAB GLASTEAM AB

2011- 2016 FUNCTIONAL TESTER

Work with Data entry and products